

20 / 09 / 1996 - Valencia, Spain.

# **ABOUT ME**

Digital Marketing Specialist with Full Stack skills, expert in Web Development.

communicator Effective passionate about various activities in the fields of technology and entertainment.

Dedicated to providing quality creative and solutions to enhance the success of the projects in which I participate.

#### MORE INFORMATION

#### Availability:

- Full Time
- Hybrid
- Remote Work

# **LANGUAGES**

Spanish: Native.

Catalan: Native (Valencian).

English: Professional.

#### CONTACT



<u>gonagb.com</u>



+34 636 767 282



gonagb96@gmail.com



GitHub.com/gonagb



<u>linkedin.com/in/gonagb/</u>

# **Gonzalo Aguirre Boix**

# Marketing Manager | Junior Full Stack Developer

# WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Full Stack Developer**

Fourvenues. | Mar 2024 - May 2024

Performing Intranet development tasks as Frontend.

MVC programming. APIs consumption. Version control with GitLab. Event management software for entertainment venues. HND Internship.

Technologies: Angular, Node.js, Tailwind CSS, Chart.js, MongoDB, Docker.

#### **Head of Marketing**

Prevenpyme S.L. | Apr 2023 - Feb 2024

Digital Marketing. Graphic Designer. Data Analyst. Social Media Specialist. Event planner. Contact with companies (Collaborations). Documentation designer. Product placement.

#### **PlayStation Promoter**

Sony Europe | Nov 2022 - Jan 2023

PlayStation promoter for the Christmas campaign 22/23 in FNAC San Agustín.

# **Gaming Room Operator**

Cirsa Gaming Corp. | Jul 2020 - Nov 2020

Bookmaker, debt collector and customer service.

# **Marketing Manager**

Terreta Games | Sep 2018 - Jan 2020

Responsible of PR and marketing campaigns of the company.

#### **Head of PR & VIP Assistant**

Grupo Las Animas | Sep 2012 - Jun 2019

Ticket sales, event organization, VIP manager, PR manager, and various public relationship tasks.

#### **Marketing Assistant**

Espacio Arcade | Apr 2018 - Jun 2018

HND Marketing and Advertising Internships.

Responsible of SEO positioning on apps.

#### **Shop Assistant**

WORTEN S.L: | Nov 2014 - Feb 2015

Computer and electronics section.

# **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

Higher National Diploma in FullStack Software Development (Spain) IMF Smart Education Capitol | Sep 2022 - Jun 2024

Higher National Diploma in Marketing and Advertising (Spain)

IMF Smart Education Capitol | Sep 2016 - Jul 2018

**Vocational Education and Training in Business Activities** 

Escuela Profesional Xavier | Sep 2013 - Jul 2015

#### INFORMATION

Hardware knowledge. Software development, design and architecture.

Technical problem solving. Team collaboration. Research and technological updating.

SEO and positioning. Constant learning and development. Version control. Gaming and eSports

Branding and brand image.

#### **TECHNOLOGIES**













Stack MERN/MEAN









